var questions = [
  {
    question: "Which sense is developed first in newborns?",
    choices: [
      "Hearing",
      "Touch",
      "Taste",
      "Smell"
    ],
    answer: "Hearing"
  },
  {
    question: "When does a baby start to smile socially?",
    choices: [
      "After one year",
      "2-5 months",
      "4-8 weeks",
      "7-8 months"
    ],
    answer: "4-8 weeks"
  },
  {
    question: "Excluding medical cost, how much does it cost on average to raise a child for the first year in the USA?",
    choices: [
      "$10,000",
      "$3,000",
      "$15,000",
      "$7,000"
    ],
    answer: "$7,000"
  },
  {
    question: "How long does it take on average for a man to change a diaper on a newborn?",
    choices: [
      "45 seconds flat!",
      "2 minutes",
      "1 minutes 7 seconds",
      "1 minute 36 seconds"
    ],
    answer: "1 minute 36 seconds"
  },
  {
    question: "What is the essential ingredient in a diaper cake?",
    choices: [
      "lavender chocolate",
      "matcha tea cream",
      "diapers",
      "vanilla extract"
    ],
    answer: "diapers"
  },
  {
    question: "Newborns don’t have this body part:",
    choices: [
      "Kneecaps",
      "skull",
      "elbows",
      "hipbone"
    ],
    answer: "Kneecaps"
  },
  {
    question: "What is the word for mother in Japanese?",
    choices: [
      "Okaasan",
      "Imouto",
      "Otousan",
      "Oniisan"
    ],
    answer: "Okaasan"
  },
  {
    question: " Which evil mythological character is kept at a bay with a lullaby?",
    choices: [
      "The boogie man",
      "Lilith",
      "Mephistopheles",
      "Dionysus"
    ],
    answer: "Lilith"
  },
  {
    question: "Which oldies music group came up with the the hit song “Baby Love?”",
    choices: [
      "The Supremes",
      "The Ronettes",
      "The Chantels",
      "The Temptations"
    ],
    answer: "The Supremes"
  },
  {
    question: "How do you say ‘little girl’ in Spanish?",
    choices: [
      "neko",
      "niño",
      "niña",
      "mujer"
    ],
    answer: "niña"
  }
]